小子 你给个决斗的理由
Explain something to me, blanco,
前一分钟 你刚为他捡回性命
One minute you plead for your friend's life,
后一分钟 你又要结果了他
and the next minute you nt to take it.
这家伙
This man
这家伙根本不是我的朋友
this man is no friend of mine
你女友发生的事情和我无关
What happened to your girlfriend has nothing
她名字叫 莎拉
Her name was Sara
她是个好人
And she was a good person.
要不是因为你
And she'd still be alive
她活得好好的
if it wasn't for you.
这么说是为了复仇咯?
So it's revenge, eh, b?
一报还一报
An eye for an eye?
一旦做出决斗的决定 就不能收回来
Once you make such a declaration there's no going back.
没什么好顾虑的了
There's nothing to go back to.
很好
Good.
那么就开始决斗吧
Then we have a fight.
你们俩个马上去
Now, both of you,
整理所属物品
go and assign your belongings,
然后祈祷上苍站在你这边
and pray to whatever god is yours.
15分钟后回来
Come back here in 15 minutes.
斗 斗 斗
Fight, fight, fight, fight
fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight fight
你还需要别的帮助吗?
You need anymore help?
你帮的忙够多的了
You've done more than enough.
老兄 接着这个
Here, take that, man.
虽说钱不多 但足够你重新开始了
It's not a lot, but it's enough to get you started.
不 不行 我不能接受这钱
Oh, no, no, I can't take this.
我这么做是因为我想帮你们
I did this because I wanted to help you guys.
去买辆车 买张大巴车票什么的
Hey, buy a car, get a bus ticket,
随你怎样办 就是离开这就行
do whatever, just get out of here.
多谢了
Thanks.
我去加些油 行吗?
I'm going to get so gas, okay?
我们在前头会合
I'll meet you in the front.
好的
All right.
好运
Good luck.
同祝
You too.
她和你一起去交换人质?
Is she coming with you to do the exchange?
是的
Yeah.
你觉得这样合适吗?
You think that's a good idea?
我是说如果有什么麻烦的话
I mean, what if something goes wrong
-她还会受伤呢 -我需要个保障
and she gets hurt? I need some incentive
以防 惠斯勒 耍什么鬼把戏
just in case Whistler doesn't want to go quietly.
你觉得这一切都能平稳度过?
You think any of this is going to go down quiet?
就这样把LJ还给你了?
They're just going to give you LJ
我怎么想的根本无关紧要
just like that? Doesn't matter what I think.
我很清楚这帮子人会怎么干
I know what these people are capable of.
我不会拿我儿子的命去赌博的
I'm not going to gamble with my son's life.
或许你根本不需要什么赌博
Maybe you don't have to.
阿历克斯
Alex.
什么事
Yeah.
15分钟后就到审判厅了
We'll be arriving at the courthouse in about 15 minutes.
然后紧接着就开始听证会
Then the hearing will begin shortly.
所有这一切马上就能了结了
All and all this whole thing will be done within the hour.
很好
Good.
听上去很不错
That sounds good.
那么这场交易中
So with this deal
他们到底想从我这获得什么呢?
what specifically are they expecting from me?
他们需要知道所有这一切
They need to knoeverything.
关于总统的 关于组织的事情
About the President, about the company.
他们需要确认你手上有
They want to confirm that you have
确凿的能证明他们犯罪的信息
viable incriminating information
而且你还需要配合去做证
and that you can be a cooperative witness.
如果我完全配合的话
If I cooperate fully
我不会只起诉他们有罪
I won't just be incriminating them.
你担心你会受到牵连
You're worried about all those skeletons in your closet,
你有完全赦免权
but you have full immunity.
所有这一切都会没事的
Everything will be fine.
你只需要说出事实真相就行
All you have to do is tell the truth.
保持冷静
Stay calm.
最好活动下筋骨热热身
Better knuckle up.
听着 我不知道你是怎么想的
Look, I don't know what you're thinking,
但是杀了我
but killing me is not
-于事无补 -别紧张
going to solve your problem. Relax.
我不会杀你的
I'm not going to kill you.
那刚才那幕又是为了什么?
Then what the hell was all that about?
你如果想不被发现 从这里越狱出去
You want to make it out of here without being seen,
你就需要转移视线 就像现在这样
you need a diversion. Now we have one.
你昏头了 你不知道他们还在那边等着
You're off your head. Do you know that? They're waiting
我们没时间争这个 快3点了
We don't have time for this. It's almost 3:00,
意味着塔楼哨兵现在应该被迷药放倒了
and that means the tower guard should be drugged by now.
3:13分时 阳光会照射在另一哨塔上
At 3:13, the sun's going to hit the other guard tower.
有了所需的掩护 机不可失 时不再来
We'll have the cover we need. It's now or never.
听着 迈克 我
Listen, Michael, I, uh
刚才关于莎拉的话 不是那个意思
I meant what I said about Sara.
换作我 就绝口不提那名字了
If I were you I wouldn'tention that name again.
我们现在就出去 然后用你交换我侄子
We're getting out of here now, and then I'm trading you for my nephew.
然后我会去查清楚
And then I'm going to find out
真凶是谁的
who's responsible for taking her life
然后血债血还
and I'm taking theirs.
YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
最新最快字幕下载请登录：www.YYeTs.net
■
字幕：YYeTs人人影视字幕组  后期：梁良
-听着 斯科菲尔德 -现在不是时候
Listen, Scofield Not now.
我只是 求你了
I just please.
你在外面说的我听到了
I heard you out there in the yard.
关于莎拉的事情
Is that true
是不是真的?
about Sara?
是的
Yes.
怎么会 我是说
That's not I mean it's
她怎么 ?
What'd she ?
对不起 迈克
I'm sorry, Michael.
我是这个意思
I mean it.
她是好人
She was a good person.
对不起
I'm sorry.
怎么了?
Is something wrong?
如果有人问起
If anyone asks,
告诉他们油箱漏油 好吗?
just tell them your fuel pump's leaking, all right?
不 不 我要和你一起去海边
No, no, no, I'm going to the beach with you.
不 我需要你来把风
No. I need you to keep a lookout.
他们来了我会告诉你的 好吗?
When they get here I'll call you, all right?
如果今天一切顺利
If everything works out today,
你和我 都能得到想要的
you and me we're both going to get what we want.
留在这里
Stay here.
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
没事
That's okay.
我知道你是在工作
I know you're just doing your job.
我保证你和我一样
I bet you're as ready
都已经受够了
for this over with as I am.
知道吗 我们从巴拿马出来之后
Hey, you know, once we get out of Panama,
我和我爸爸 还有叔叔
me and my dad and my uncle
我们要开个潜水商店
we're going to open up a scuba shop somewhere.
-在海边造个房子 -听起来不错
Build a house on the beach Lovely.
每天去游泳
go swimming every day.
-我从没住在海边 -你可以住嘴了
I never lived by the ocean You can stop.
我一直想去 知道吗?
I always wanted to, you know?
我知道了
I get it.
你是有梦想的人
You're a human being
为将来打算 就那样
wi dreams, plans for the future, all that.
你能否见到那天 已经不在我的掌握
Whether you see it isn't up to me anymore.
在于你的叔叔
It's in your uncle's hands now.
所以让我们祈祷他能做到吧
So let's just hope that he does his job.
你还在等什么?
What are you waiting for?
马宏 在哪里?
Where's Mahone?
他走了
He's gone.
什么 就那么走了?
What, just like that?
为什么? 我是说 怎么会?
Why? I mean, how?
我们还是多关心一下自己吧 怎么样?
How about we worry a little bit more about us, huh?
知道吗 他是突然出去的
You know, he got out of here kind of suddenly.
我们怎么知道他不会出卖我们?
How do we know he's not ratting us out right now?
苏林斯
Sullins.
什么时候的事?
When did this happen?
-你确定吗? -好的
Are you sure? Yeah.
我来处理
I'll handle it.
有什么问题吗?
Something wrong?
几个巴拿马人有点退缩了
A couple of the Panamanians might have gotten cold feet.
有多胆小?
Exactly how cold?
他们只是需要确认
They just need some convincing.
没什么好担心的
It's nothing to worry about.
一切都会顺利的
It's all gonna work out.
同时 我们会把你带到酒店房间去
Meantime, we're gonna take you to a hotel room.
直到一小时前
Up until an hour ago,
不是说一切都搞定了
this was a done deal.
还会发生什么呢?
So what's happening?
放松 这仍旧是你最好的机会
Relax. This is still your best bet.
除非有人开的价码是
Unless someone's offering you
"无罪从索纳监狱释放"
a"get out of Sona free"card.
记好了 我们只有4分钟掩蔽时间
Now, remember, we'll only have four minutes of cover,
你一着地 就笔直跑向围栏
so once you hit the ground you run straight to the fence.
不要看上面 也别回头
Don't look up, don't look back,
不要说一个字
don't say a word.
要是他们看见我们呢?
What if they see us?
如果有人喊你停
If someone yells stop,
你就停
you stop.
就这些?
That's it?
就这些
That's it.
时间到了
It's time.
萨米去哪了?
Where's Sammy?
老大 我不知道
I dont know, Patron
那么谁先下?
So, who goes first?
你要是不活着出去 我的生命也没有意义
Right now my life isn't worth a damn without yours.
如果不是按照计划行事
If this doesn't go as planned, the first guy
先下的人就会被射杀
through that window's gonna get shot.
那个人不能是你
That guy can't be you.
我先下吧
I'll go.
我明白了
I got it.
快 快
Come on, come on, come on.
机会来了
This is it.
五
Five
四
four
三
three
二 一
two one.
阳光
The glare.
-阳光哪去了? -我不知道
Where's the glare? I don't know.
拜托
Come on
成了
This is it.
有人来了
Someone's coming.
好运
Good luck.
你也是
You, too.
我们快失去阳光了
We're losing the light.
会去 快回去
Go back. Go back
快回去
Go back
动作快
Come on Come on
这是我们唯一的机会
That was our only chance.
见鬼
Damn it
把他们找出来
Find out where they are.
听到他们在外面喧哗吗 在等着我们
Do you hear 'em out there? They're waiting for us.
-迟早得出去 -我知道
It's only a matter of time. I know. Come on.
这该死的东西解不开
The damn thing's not coming off
外国佬
Hey, gringos
出来决斗了
Come out and play.
快 快啊
Come on Come on
该死的 躲得了初一躲不过十五的
Nowhere to hide, malditos
外国佬
Gringos
出来决斗了
Come out and play
我们必须离开 这儿他们找不到
We've got to go. They can't find us here.
但这个怎么处理?
But what about this?
遮一下
Stash it
但这个怎么处理?
Come on
快啊
走
Go.
臭小子 你要去哪里?
Where are you off to, Backra?
你们俩去哪里了?
Where you boys been?
洗手间?
The bathroom?
这一切都是
This has all been
一场巨大的误会
a terrible mistake.
是吗?
Has it been?
我们的问题都解决了
We've, uh, we've worked it out.
没有必要再进行决斗了
There's no need to take this any further.
显然你不太明白
You clearly don't understand
我不能让你们的愚昧在这里肆虐
I can't have your foolishness spread in this place.
我给过你这么多机会放弃决斗
I gave you every chance to pull out.
求你了
Please.
我们都知道规矩的
We know the rules
两人决斗
Two men go in,
一人活着出去
one man comes out
现在
Now,
决斗必须开始
this quarrel must be settled.
去吧
Let's go.
斗 斗 斗
Fight Fight Fight Fight Fight Fight
你们两个绅士在等什么呢?
What are you gentlemen waiting for?
你们不动手的话 我来帮忙
You two don't make this more interesting, I will.
对不起了 如果只能有一个人活着
Sorry, mate if only one of us is getting out
什么情况?
How's it look?
LJ在货车后面
They got LJ in the back of the van.
-他看起来还好吧? -我想是的
He seem all right to you? Yeah, I think so.
好吧 他们有几个人?
All right, how many people they got?
有个司机 有个保镖 就那么多
She's got a driver and a bodyguard that's it.
很好 你观察一下四周
All right. You know I appreciate you hanging around, man
兄弟 我们一起开始的行动
Hey, we started this together, bro.
所以也一起来搞定
Let's finish it that way.
快来吧 迈克
Come on, Michael.
你在哪啊
Where are you?
你在这干吗?
What you doing here?
你应该在那里把风的
You're supposed to be keeping watch.
只是确认下 看看是否一切正常
Just checking, making sure everything is all right.
他们行动有点延迟 没什么
They're running a bit late, that's all.
下一步呢?
So, what's the plan?
游出去 等警察过去了 然后
You gonna swim out, wait for the police to pass, and
在某个地方上船?
meet with a boat somewhere?
差不多就是那样
Something like that.
那再然后呢?
And then what?
知道吗 你得回到
You know what, you need to get back
-车那儿去 -不许动
to the car Don't move.
让人吃惊啊
I'm impressed.
拿着枪指着我
You've actually got the guts to look me in the eye
还有勇气跟我对视
as you stab me in the back.
你会怎么做 打死我?
What are you going to do, shoot me?
别动 我不能眼看着你把詹姆斯
Don't. I can't let you hand over
送到那些人手上
James to those people.
你得考虑考虑你在干嘛
You need to think about what you're doing.
我想过了
I have
在你告诉我他们对莎拉做了什么之后
Every since you told me what they did to Sara.
他们到了之后 詹姆斯和我就离开
When they get here, James and I, we're leaving.
去哪?
Where to?
我不知道 一个他们找不到的地方
I don't know. Somewhere they won't find us.
那么这一段时间以来 你都在耍我
So, this whole time, you played me.
就像你在耍我一样
Like you've been playing me.
带我来这里 帮你把风?
Bringing me here to be your lookout?
不过没什么
But it's okay.
我们来这里都是
We were both here doing what we had to
为了我们深爱的人做该做的事
for the people we love.
你这么做的话 你也等于亲手杀了我儿子
You do this, you may as well be shooting my son yourself.
对不起
I'm sorry.
他们这个时候该出来了 有消息没?
They should be out by now. Any sign?
一切都很安静
All quiet.
你准备给他们多少时间?
How much longer do you want to give them?
我知道你下半辈子
I know you wanted to live
想住在海边
by an ocean your whole life.
真可惜
Sad to think
你只能葬身在海边了
the closest you'll get is being buried under one.
你不会杀了我的
You're not gonna kill me.
-是吗? -你需要我
Oh? You need me.
你已经杀了莎拉
You already killed Sara.
我要再有什么事的话
Anything happens to me,
你手上就没有筹码了
you're out of bargaining chips.
如果迈克今天不把惠斯勒救出来
If Michael doesn't get Whistler out today,
我就不再需要什么筹码了
I won't need to bargain anymore.
你们都要死
You'll all be dead.
胡塔多?
Hurtdo?
胡塔多? 你在哪?
Hurtdo?Where you at?
呼叫 罗丹
Hey,Roldan.
最好找人看看
Better send someone to check
1号岗的胡塔多
on Hurtado in Tower One.
呼叫他没反应
He is not answering his radio
我这里也看不到他
and I don't have a visual.
收到
Confirmed.
我们会派人过去的
We'll send a couple men over.
狠狠的踢他 斯科菲尔德
Kick him in the junk, Scofield
你们在等什么? 这里没有平局的说法
What are you looking for, boy There are no draws here
如果没有一个人来了结的话
If this isn't finished by one of you,
我会下来了结你们两个
I'm coming down to finish both of you.
胡塔多?
Hurtdo?
你在干嘛?
What are you doing over there?
什么 你居然当班的时候睡觉?
What, are you sleeping on the job?
不 我不知道发生什么了
No, I don't know what happened.
下手吧
End it.
上帝啊 请原谅我
God God forgive me.
他们这个时候该到了
They should have been here by now.
或许他们已经出来了 正在赶来
Maybe they get out. They should be on their way.
-他们失手了 -那我们现在该干嘛?
They didn't make it. So what do we do now?
我管不着你怎么办
I don't care what you do,
我要开着车子走
but I'm taking the car.
什么?
What?
发生什么事了?
What the hell's going on?
把手放到头上
Put your hands up on your head
你 下来 到这里来
You come down here.
马上
Now
我们要找出是谁干的
We are going to find out who is behind this.
什么事?
What?
你是不是该告诉我发生什么了?
Were you going to let me know what the hell's going on?
林肯?
Lincoln?
我在听
I'm here.
很好 他们在哪?
Good. Where are they?
他们在我车上
They're in the car with me.
我听到警报声了
I heard the alarm.
警报前他们就跑得很远了
They were long gone before that thing went off.
好吧 如果他们开了个好头
Well, if they had such a head start,
你干嘛要磨蹭这么久?
why are you so far behind?
听着 你想让我开车的时候和你说话?
Listen, do you want me to talk to your drive?
让惠斯勒听电话
I want you to put Whistler on the phone.
什么?
What?
让他听电话
Put him on.
他在后备箱里
He's in the trunk.
不过 如果你强烈要求的话
But, if you feel that strongly about it,
我可以把他拖出来 你们俩可以稍微聊聊
I can pull over and you two can have a Nice little talk.
如果运气好的话 或许会有警察过来
If we're real lucky, maybe some cops will swing by.
我肯定警察也想和他谈谈的
I'm sure they'd like a word, too.
知道吗? 准备好放LJ
You know what? Just get LJ ready.
有人要逃出去 并且袭击了我的人
Whoever tried to escape assaulted one of my men.
众所周知 任何对巴拿马士兵
And, as you know, any attempt on the life
构成生命威胁的袭击
of a Panamanian soldier
都是死刑
warrants the death penalty.
是212号囚室的人干的
This attempt was made from cell #212.
如果没记错的话
And if memory serves,
那个囚室是你的人 对吧?
that cell belongs to members of your crew, no?
你
You.
你是那个送奶人吧
You are one of the Milkman's boys.
那是你的囚室吧?
Is it your cell?
我认为这是个肯定的答案
I'm going to take that as a yes.
我一直认为我们是亲密伙伴 你和我
I thought we were compadres, you and I.
我让你做你的生意 招你的妓
I let you run your business, have your whores.
没有水的时候
When you asked me for your own personal supply of water
还有停电的时候 我都满足你了吧?
when the lumbing went down, did I not provide it?
你让我切断电话
When you asked me to get rid
使他们无从非法运毒进来
of the phones, make them contraband,
以此来控制这里的交易
so you could control the trade in here,
我难道没满足你么?
did I not comply?
我做这一切都是为了你
I do all this for you.
而作为交易条件 我只要你为我
And in exchange, you were to do one thing
做一件事
for me.
管好这些人
Keep these men in line
也许我们看错人了
Maybe we just backed the wrong horse.
也许别人更适合这份工作
Perhaps there is another in here better suited for the job.
祝你好运 兄弟
Good luck, Bredda.
你知道我们中没人想
You know none of us tried
从那间牢房越狱
to break out of that cell.
我知道
I do.
但你一定知道只有一个人
Then you must know there's only one guy here
会愚蠢到想去试试
foolish enough to try.
很高兴看到你恢复如初
Nice to see you back in form.
谢谢
Thanks.
苏林斯 那有什么新消息吗?
Any news from Sullins?
他正在处理此事
He's working on it.
别人说什么都没关系
It doesn't matter what people say.
他们怎么说?
What do they say?
-你知道他们怎么说吗 -怎么说?
You know people, how they talk. About?
他们说是你杀了那些人
The men, the ones they say you killed.
这是真的吗?
Is it true?
如果是真的 你可以和我说说
Because, if it is, you can talk to about it.
真是这样吗?
Is that a fact?
是的 你可以相信我
Yes. You can trust me.
这么明说了吧
So let me get this straight.
苏林斯 让你来扮白脸?
Sullins sends you to be good cop?
不是这样的
That's not what this is.
其实从来就没有什么交易 对吗?
There never was a deal, was there?
苏林斯 只是想让我认罪
Sullins just wants me to confess
那他就有更多的指控理由遣送我回美国
so hcan bring me up on more charges back in the States.
交易很合理
The deal is legit.
那听证会本应该是
The hearing was supposed to be
我们离开监狱一小时后开的
an hour after we left the prison,
而我还在等
and I'm still waiting.
为什么你不把一切告诉我 费丽舍?
So why don't you just come clean, Felicia, huh?
看在以前的交情份上 怎样?
For old times' sake? How about it?
那你怎么不看在老交情份上配合呢?
How about you do me the same courtesy, Alex?
我不傻 我弟弟只是你们利用的工具
I'm not blind. My brother was a user.
我早就知道了
I can smell the stuff a mile away.
你不是想说我隐瞒什么吧?
Don't you accuse me of being the one who's hiding something.
我刚从广播中证实了
Hey, I just got confirmation from the radio.
狱警盘点过 监狱周围也被监控起来
The guards took a head count and they secured the perimeter.
今天没人逃出了过
No one made it out of there today.
苏克雷 怎么样了?
Sucre, what's going on?
看起来他们正准备离开
Looks like they're packing up.
不论你做什么
Whatever you do
不要让他们带走LJ 好吗?
don't let them take LJ, all right?
林肯? 林肯?
Linc? Linc?
苏克雷?
Sucre?
现在就离开
Get the hell out of here now.
小心
Look out
爸
Dad
放她走
Let her go
把枪放下 否则我开枪杀死她
Drop it or I swear to God I'll put a bullet in her head
-现在放他走 你放他走 -爸
Now you let him go You let him go now Dad
LJ 我保证我会把你救出来
LJ, I'm going to get you out of this, I promise.
你对儿子许下一个实现不了的诺言吗?
You sure you want to make promises to your son you can't keep?
闭嘴
Watch your mouth.
我告诉你一个小秘密
I'll let you in on a little secret.
自从你选择
When you choose
这么解决问题 你就该知道
this line of work, you know it's all going to come down
会发生现在这一幕
to a moment like this.
杀了我吧
So kill me.
放他走
Let him go.
-放了他 -杀了他
Let him go Kill him.
杀了他
Kill him.
爸
Dad
你对我做什么都可以
It doesn't matter what you do to me.
计划失败了
The operation failed.
放下的你枪 林肯
So put your gun down, Linc.
杀了他
Kill him.
爸
Dad
不要
No
再给我一次机会
Give me one more shot.
做什么?
To do what?
让我查出究竟索纳监狱里发生了什么事情
Let me find out what happened in Sona.
让我和迈克谈谈
Let me talk to Michael.
我们可以救出惠斯勒的
We can still get Whistler.
我们能办到的
We can make this happen.
我们能办到的 我们
We can make this happen. We
我们可以这么做
We can do this.
把他带上车
Put him in the van.
苏克雷
Sucre
你怎么样?
You all right?
发生了什么?
What happened?
裹尸袋
Body bags.
该发生的
Look, what happened out there
都发生了 都结束了
Happened out there. It's over.
那好
All right then.
如你所知
Right, just so you know,
我没能逃出去
I wouldn't have gone through with it.
如果幸运的话 我们不会被发现
Lucky for us, we'll never have to find out.
那现在我们怎么做?
So what do we do now?
你知道你在哪里么 小子
You know where are you, boy?
我不是医生 但我可以猜猜看
Well, I'm no doctor, You but I'm just guessingboy.
你妈一定是有天晚上喝多了才
your mother had a little bit too much to drink one night
继续说呀
Keep talking
下一个就轮到你了
and you're going to be next.
你选个死法吧 老兄?
How you want it, brother?
快的还是慢的
Fast or slow?
我稍后会亲自动手
I think I later handle this one myself.
你有孩子么 斯科菲尔德先生?
Do you have children, Mr. Scofield?
会有的
Maybe someday.
会有个非常乐观的家伙步你后尘
That's very optimistic for a man in your position.
我有五个孩子
Myself, I have five.
三个小子 两个丫头
Three boys, two girls.
我常常给他们讲的一个故事
Now I used to tell them a story
我想在你们国家里
I believe in your country
他们管它叫"狼来了"
they call it,"The Boy Who Cried Wolf."
你知道那个故事么?
You know it?
你知道这个故事的寓意
Well, then you know the moral of that story
即使撒谎者说的是实话
is even when liars tell the truth,
他们也是不可信的
they can never be believed.
你命悬一线 小子
But your life's on the line, boy.
你想越狱么 斯科菲尔德先生?
Are you trying to break out of this prison, Mr. Scofield?
不想
No.
你真准备越狱么?
Are you trying to break out of this prison?
我们都知道这是不可能的
We both know that's not possible.
-回答我 -你想让我说什么?
Answer me What do you want me to say?
我想让你告诉我事实 我要听实话
I want you to tell me the truth. I want to hear it.
-你想找个理由干掉我 -不是 小子
You want a reason to kill me. No, boy
我已经有一个很好的理由干掉你了
I have good reason to kill you.
因为你 我已经不可能
Because of you, it's no longer possible
有力地管理这个监狱
for me to effectively govern this prison.
不管是否承认
Justified or not,
人们已经不服我了
the men no longer have faith in me.
我只能做一件事
That leaves only one thing for me to do
来保命
to guarantee my survival.
你可以着手越狱 斯科菲尔德先生
You are breaking out of this prison, Mr. Scofield.
你要带上我
And you're taking me with you.
我得到一些好消息
Well, I've got some good news
还有些更好的消息
and I've got some better news.
让我们从好消息开始
Let's start with the good.
巴拿马人方面已经做出让步
Panamanians are back on board.
更好的消息呢?
And the better news?
你可以在
You're going to get to have
这张床上好好睡上一觉了
a really Nice sleep on that bed.
我还以为
I thought that I
我会听到可以乘飞机回美国的消息
After the hearing I was going to be on a plane back to the U.S.
你说过
You said
我是说过 你会回去的
I did, and you will be,
但是现在开听证会太晚了
but it's just too late to do the hearing now.
那是我们明早要做的第一件事情
We'll get to it first thing tomorrow.
-明早? -听起来不错
Tomorrow morning? Sounds about right.
拜托 可有什么方式方法
Please is there something, is there anything
能让事情进展顺利的吗?
that we can do to help speed things up?
当精灵满足了你的愿望
When a genie grants you a wish
你不会还摧他立马兑现吧
you don't really tell him to make it snappy.
这个听证会
This hearing
今天就要开
needs to happen today.
听证会 需要马上进行
The hearing needs needs to happen right now
看你说的
Listen to you.
你真的难以置信
You know, you are unbelievable.
我进了全力
I have dropped everything
才同意她
to come down her
把你拉出火坑
and drag your sorry ass
你不懂么
out of that hellhole You don't understand.
-我们已经说好了 -我等不及了
I've made you a deal. I can't I can't wait.
我等不及了
I can't wait.
你知道 我很高兴
You know, I am so glad
促成此行
I have made this trip
来帮助你敬仰的同事
to help your esteemed colleague.
我真可笑
I am just tickled.
把他铐起来
Cuff him.
有必要么?
Is that necessary?
把他铐起来
Cuff him.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不能再等了
I can't wait.
看见惠斯勒了吗?
Hey, have you seen Whistler?
没看见
No.
我尽心尽力工作
I spent my whole career
想方设法把坏人关在牢里
trying to keep bad people behind bars.
似乎通过我的工作
Like somehow by doing my job
我能让世界变得更美好
I was making the world a better place.
接着呢
And then
就发生了像莎拉这样的事
then you hear about what happened to someone like Sara.
现在看起来好像外面的坏人
Damn if it doesn't seem like there's more bad people
比这里还要多
out there than in here.
我警告过兄弟俩 如果他们失败了会怎样
I warned the brothers what would happen if they failed.
如果我现在给他们更多的时间
If I give them more time now, I may as well hand them
不如给他们一并捎上香烟和避孕套
a condom and a cigarette to go with it.
我大老远的来这儿
You know, I came all the way down here.
你最起码应该给我点儿意见
The least you could do is offer me an opinion.
我以为我们说好了你不会来这儿
I thought we agreed it was best for you to not come here.
我以为你会在7天之内出来
And I thought you needed to be out in seven days.
我想知道这次耽搁会如何影响大局
I need to know how this delay is going to affect things.
那不会好过 但是还有希望
Well, it won't be comfortable, but it will be possible.
谢谢你 詹姆斯
Oh, well, thank you, James,
但是那不会毁了我的信心
but that doesn't exactly ravage me with confidence.
那什么会?
And what would?
你坐上飞机逃之夭夭
Your ass on a plane.
再给我4天
Four more days.
如果我出去了 我还可以做到
If I'm out of here by then, I can still do it.
相信我 不会有事儿的
Trust me. It'll be fine.
我会告诉他们的
I'll let the brothers know.
格瑞成
Gretchen.
索菲亚呢
About Sofia
她很好
She's fine.
布鲁斯对她非常之好
Burrows is taking real good care of her.
好运 詹姆斯
Good luck, James.